听好了 同志们 这是一份时刻表
All right, everyone, here's the schedule.
关于今天的冒险天地之旅
For today's trip to super adventureland.
我把每件事的安排都安排妥当了
I planned everything to the minute.
我看看 八点五十七启程
Okay, depart promptly at 8:57 A.M.;
九点三十三到达冒天停车场
Arrive S.A.L. Parking lot, 9:33 A.M.
-有问题 -冒天代表“冒险天地”
- Question. - S.A.L. Stands for "super adventureland."
谢谢
Thank you.
我可不想带查莉去孩子王国
I don't want to take Charlie to kiddie kingdom.
小孩都认为我是个巨人 还往我身上爬
Kids there always think I'm a giant and try and climb me.
继续 十点四十一 老妈在
Okay, 10:41 a. M.... Mom throws up.
沃利海象垃圾箱里狂吐不止
In Wally walrus trash receptacle.
用的着这么详细吗
That's kind of specific.
无敌转轮外面有个垃圾箱
That's the trash can that's right outside the super spinner.
我们十点三十九的时候会去玩
Which we'll be riding at 10:39.
说的有理
Then I guess this is right.
嘿 我怎么没在这上面看到爱国广场
Hey, I don't see patriotic Plaza on this thing.
我想看看新的开国元勋展示会
I want to see the new founding-fathers exhibit.
爹啊 如果开国元勋
Dad, when the founding fathers.
能在五秒内加速到九十迈
Can go zero to 90 in five seconds.
还能让老妈狂吐不止 我就会安排它的
And make mom barf, they'll make the schedule.
-嗨 大家好 干什么呢 -嘿 宝贝
- Hi, guys, what's going on? - Hey, honey.
你怎么还没穿好衣服 我们快要去冒险天地了
Why aren't you dressed? We're going to super adventureland.
噢 天啊 是今天吗 我还想找份工作呢
Oh, man, that's today? I was gonna look for a job.
那就 明天再找 今天可是个重要的日子
Well, do it tomorrow. Today's a big day.
我想让全家一起出动
I want the whole family together.
你就想拉我入伙弄团购 是吧
You just want me there for the big-family discount, right?
-被你猜中了 -我都不用猜
- And there's that. - Yep.
好了 咱们能谈正题吗
All right, can we move this along?
我只预留了三分钟来争论老爸的团购计划
I only budgeted three minutes for an argument about dad's pness.
不如这样 用我们省下来的时间 去趟爱国广场...
Oh, hey, with the time we save, maybe a visit to patriotic a...
我们不会去的
We're not going!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十六集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E26  Return to Super Adventure Land
难以置信我们终于到了
Can't believe we're finally here.
好了 咱们全家要好好玩玩了
All right. Time for some family fun.
没错
Right.
回见
See ya.
那只青蛙一直盯着你
That frog is staring at you.
我看见了 让我感觉浑身不自在
I know. It given me a weird feeling.
-我也是 我们走 查莉 -搞什么
- Me too. Let's go, Charlie. - What?
嘿
Hey.
-啊 噢 -嗨 我的泰迪宝贝
- Dah! Oh. - Hi, Teddy bear.
-嗨 艾米特 -我现在在这里工作
- Hi, Emmett. - I'm working here now.
不错
Oh good.
这么说来你不是穿着一身青蛙的服装
So you're not just cruising around super adventureland.
-在冒险天地里瞎转悠 -不是
- In a frog costume? - Nope.
-我其实是只跳跳蛙 -跳跳
- I'm actually hoppy the frog. - Hoppy?
每次当人们念我的名字时 我就要跳一下
Every time somebody says my name, I have to hop.
除此之外 还算是个好工作
Other than that it's a great job.
我只要随便溜溜 然后每个小时表演五分钟
I just walk around, do a five minutes show once an hour.
而且酬劳还不错
And it pays really well.
那你知道这里还缺人吗
Oh hey, are there any openings?
因为我想攒钱买车
Because I've been trying to save up for a car.
正好有个人辞职了 想让我帮你看看能不能加入么
Actually someone just quit. Want me to see if I can get you in?
太好了 谢谢了 艾米特 我好想“跳跳”啊
Yeah. Thanks, Emmett. That would make me "hoppy."
能别跟着我了吗 我不是什么巨人
Would you please stop following me? I am not a giant.
太爽了
That was awesome!
今天简直棒极了
This has been the best day ever.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
宝贝 我排了六个小时的队
Honey, I stood in line for six hours.
坐过山车上下翻滚了三次
I've been upside down three times.
我坐着歇会儿
I'm sitting.
好吧 我还想在回家之前再玩一次
All right. I want to go on one more ride before we go home.
我爱死冒险天地了
I love super adventureland!
嘿 打扰一下 我是丹尼·弗拉佛曼
Hey. Um, excuse me. I'm Danny flufferman.
我是冒险天地的市场总监
I'm the director of marketing here for super adventureland.
我们想找你拍条广告
How would you like to be in a commercial?
真的 但我不是演员
Really? But I'm not an actor.
我们知道 没关系 我们不想要演员
Yeah, no no, we don't want actors.
我们想找一个真心喜欢冒险天地的真实小孩
We want real kids who really love super adventureland.
如果你同意了 我将送你一年的免费门票
And if you do it, I could throw in a free one-year pass,
周末 假期最好别来 娱乐设施不附加在内
Not good on weekends, holidays; rides not included.
好吧
All right.
等一下 等一下 怎么个情况
Whoa whoa whoa whoa. What's going on?
老妈 这家伙想找我拍条冒险天地的广告
Mom, this guy wants me to be in a commercial for super adventureland.
等一下 别着急 大家
Whoa whoa. Slow down, everybody.
听好了 我反对这件事
Okay look, I'm not agreeing to anything.
我曾在娱乐圈混过一段时间
Now I've had some experience in show business,
现在我可不想让我儿子牵扯其中
And I don't want my son anywhere near it.
噢 那太遗憾了
Oh, that's too bad really,
因为这是一个关于母子的广告
Because it was going to be a commercial about the boy and his mother.
我同意了
I'll do it.
等一下 是我们同意了
Wait, we'll do it.
无所谓了 我在哪签字
Whatever. Where do I sign?
这里
Oh.
嘿 PJ 什么这么香
Hey, P.J., what smells so good?
-老妈的肉馅糕 -说真的 什么这么香
- Mom's meat loaf. - Seriously, what smells so good?
这个 尝尝
Go on, try it.
我的七舅姥爷 这绝对不是你老妈的肉馅糕
Whoa. Whoa, this is not your mother's meat loaf.
我是说 这东西 呃 呃 怎么说呢
I mean, this has got, um um um... what's the word?
-美味佳肴 -没错 就是这词
- Flavor. - Flavor! Yes.
老妈在医院加班
Mom was working late at the hospital.
所有的食材都在这里 所以我就下厨试试
The ingredients were all here, so I gave it a shot.
下厨试试
You gave it a shot?
儿子 你这简直是干的太漂亮了 就像全垒打
Kid, you just hit a home run.
全垒打
A home run?
少来 老爸 你说的有点夸张了
Come on, dad, I think you're exaggerating.
我有帮忙
I helped.
没错 没错 你帮了
Yes. Yes, you did.
我是主力
I did most of the work.
PJ 你在烹饪方面有天赋
P.J., you... you have a real gift.
-嘿 你觉得还能再做一次吗 -这个 不清楚
- Hey, you think you can do this again? - Well, I don't know.
因为我知道你老妈以后还会加班的
Because I'm pretty sure your mother's going to be working late again,
特别是如果我给她的主任打电话的话
Especially if I call her supervisor.
噢 巧克力蛋糕好了
Oh, my brownies are done.
巧克力蛋糕
Brownies?
我马上回来 我去给医院打电话
Be right back. I'm calling the hospital.
欢迎入驻冒险天地大家庭
Welcome to the super adventureland family!
-我得到工作了 -抱抱
- I got the job? - Hug?
先回答我
Answer the question.
是的 你得到工作了
Yes, you got the job.
太好了
Oh yay!
你将扮演公主
You're gonna be playing a princess.
噢 公主啊 我喜欢
Ooh! A princess? I like it.
今晚我们要表演个小节目 只有咱俩
Actually we do a little show together, just the two of us.
为什么要安排公主和青蛙来演戏啊
Why would they put a princess in a show with a frog?
没错
Oh yeah.
艾米特 请告诉我这不是
Emmett, please tell me this isn't the story.
公主吻青蛙 青蛙变王子的故事
Where the princess kisses the frog and turns him into a prince.
一天演八次
Eight times a day.
周日演九次
And nine on sundays.
你为什么不早告诉我有吻戏啊
Why didn't you tell me I'd have to kiss you?
我怕影响你是否参演这个决定
I thought it would affect your decision.
说得好 这绝对会影响我的决定
Well yeah, it totally would affect my decision.
是不是上一个女孩就因为这个而辞职了
Is this why the last girl quit?
没错
Oh yeah.
盖比 他们刚把广告的剧本发过来了
Gabe, they just sent over the script for the commercial.
-太好了 看看 -好的
- Cool, let's read it. - Okay.
“一个男孩和一位母亲
"A boy and his mother.
走在冒险天地游乐场里”
Walk through super adventureland."
然后我说 “我喜欢新版冒险天地
Then I say, "I love the new super adventureland.
过山车更快了 而且排队时间更短了”
The rides are faster and the lines are shorter."
“妈妈点头微笑”
"the mom smiles and nods."
我又说“新版冒险天地真是太棒了”
Then I say, "the new super adventureland is awesome."
我说“而且很安全”
And I say, "and safer too."
搞什么
What?
怎么搞的 我只有一句台词吗
What, that's it? That's my only line?
别难过 老妈 这广告是面向孩子的
Well, mom, the commercial's for kids.
当成年人开始说话时 孩子们会很容易走神儿的
And kids kind of start zoning out when the adults start talking.
别瞎说 成年人可以
That is not true. Adults can be very...
盖比
Gabe!
我觉得我们应该改改剧本
I think we need to make a few changes.
等等 别急 老妈 这样可以吗
Wait. Hold on, mom. Can we do that?
当然了 大家都知道剧本这东西只是个提纲
Of course. Everyone knows the script is just an outline.
我们只需要将它稍微改进一下
We'll just make a couple of small tweaks.
嗨 我是艾米·邓肯
Hi, I'm Amy Duncan,
一位四个孩子的母亲
Real-life mother of four.
如今 当你为了寻找一些家庭娱乐
And these days, when your entertainment dollar.
而感到囊中羞涩时
Is stretched tighter than a drum,
为家庭选择一项合适的娱乐项目 就变得至关重要
It's important to make the right choice for your family's fun.
这就是为什么 我 艾米·邓肯
That's why I, Amy Duncan,
总是选择冒险天地
Always choose super adventureland.
当你向往开心快乐时
When you're looking to smile
让我帮帮你
Let me give you a hand
就去冒险天地吧
It's super adventureland.
而且很安全
And safer too.
这样就好多了
That is so much better.
-嘿 PJ -嘿 老爸
- Hey, P.J. - Hey, dad.
干嘛呢
Whatcha doin'?
做作业
Homework.
作业
Homework?
晚饭前吗 没搞错吧
Before dinner? That doesn't sound right.
没办法啊 作业成山啊
Well, I've got a lot to do.
啊 懂了
Ah, got it.
懂了
Got it.
喔 喔 喔 抱歉 你听到了吗
Whoa whoa whoa, I'm sorry. Did you hear that?
听到什么
Hear... hear what?
肚子叫了
Tummy's grumbling.
你也清楚 因为你老妈又加班
You know, what with your mother working late and all...
好了 老爸 我一会儿给你做些吃的
Okay, dad, I'd cook something for you,
我要先要写完作业
But I've really gotta finish.
不如你来做饭
Or you could cook.
我给你写作业
And I could do your homework.
你还不知道呢吧 我正好在“三好学”很有造诣
And you know what? I happen to be very good at "trigometry."
是我的第二个爱好
It's my second love.
老爸 你的第二个爱好
Dad, your second love.
叫做“三角学”
Is pronounced "trigonometry."
即使我想做饭 我们也没有食材
And even if I wanted to cook, we don't have anything to make.
这下惨了 真希望我在回家的路上去了趟商店
Oh, man, I wish I had stopped off at the store on the way home.
噢 等一下
Oh, wait a minute.
我去了
I did.
好了 快点儿 放下笔 拿起炒勺
Okay, come on, you get up there and you start cooking.
我先尝尝精神食粮
And I will hit the books.
-老爸 真要这样吗 -确定一定以及肯定
- Dad, are you sure about this? - Absolutely.
哇
Wow.
密密麻麻的数字和字母
Number and letters, huh?
有的玩了
It's fun.
如果你能吻我一下 我将变成王子
If you kiss me, I'll turn into a prince.
公主不知所措了
The princess wasn't sure what to do.
此言不假
No kidding.
但是最后她决定要亲吻青蛙
But at last she decided to kiss the frog.
艾米特
Emmett?
-你是王子 -你终于知道了
- You're a prince. - You finally noticed.
我从未这么开心过
I've never felt this way before.
那是因为我在你眼中一直是只青蛙
That's because you've been looking at me like a frog.
其实我一直是你的王子
When all along I've really been your prince.
哇
Whoa!
昨晚的梦太离奇了
I had the craziest dream last night.
那好 我愿闻其详
Well, I'd love to hear about it.
但你要帮我叠那三个男子汉的内衣
While you help me fold the boys' undies.
呃 我梦到我吻了一个男生
Uh, I dreamed that I kissed this guy.
然后我瞬间爱上他了
And I fell instantly in love with him...
但是这个男生 我是绝对不可能喜欢上的
A guy that I could never possibly be in love with.
是给咱家送水的那个男生吗
Is it the guy who delivers our water?
我 我的梦 老妈 不是你的
My... my dream, mom, not yours.
蝙蝠侠 噢 是独行侠
Batman. Oh, the lone ranger.
是艾米特
It was Emmett.
他啊
Oh.
没错 但这简直是天方夜谭 对吧
Well, but that's ridiculous, right?
我怎么可能喜欢上艾米特呢
I can't possibly be in love with Emmett.
自从我记事开始 他就烦人得要命
I've known him since we were kids and he's always been super annoying.
我也说不好 泰迪 生活有时就是让人哭笑不得
I don't know, Teddy. Life can be pretty funny.
这倒是 但不会是那种玩法吧
Yeah, but not that funny, right?
好吧 你给你讲个小故事
Okay, I'm gonna tell you a little story.
纵览校园时光 有个相当烦人的孩子迷恋着老娘我
All through school, there was this really annoying kid who liked me.
但我对他一点儿也不来电
And I wanted nothing to do with him.
后来在高中 我同意和他约会了
Then in High School I agreed to go out with him.
若干约会之后 我们亲亲了
After a few dates, we kissed.
后来情况发生了天翻地覆的变化
And suddenly everything changed.
你知道那哥们是谁了吗
You know who that fellow was?
我希望是蝙蝠侠
Please say Batman.
-是你爸 -不要啊 这不是我想要的答案
- It was your father. - No! That's not what I wanted to hear.
那就抱歉了 事实就是这样
Well sorry, that's what happened.
什么 这么说来艾米特真的可能是我的王子吗
What, so Emmett might be my true love?
还是你未来四个孩子的父亲
And future father of your four children.
杀了我吧
Ah!
好香啊
Something smells good.
我在做辣椒 马上出锅儿
I'm making chili. It'll be ready in a minute.
问一下 就做了这么点儿吗
Ah. That... that all the chili you made?
是啊 不就是咱爷俩儿吗
Yeah. It's just the two of us, right?
其实
Well actually...
是咱爷五个
It's the five of us.
这是比利 乔 巴尼 他们现在正饥肠辘辘
This is Billy, Joe, Barney, and they are mighty hungry.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
鲍比 吉姆 芭比 不好意思
Bobby, Jim, Barbie, could you excuse us?
-亲爹啊 -怎么了
- Dad! - What?
难道你要让我凭空把两人份的辣椒变成五人份吗
So I'm supposed to magically turn chili for two into chili for five?
太好了
Thank you.
这要花上好几个小时
This is gonna take hours.
而且我还要写篇《呼啸山庄》的读后感
And I have a book report due on "wuthering heights."
有人看过《呼啸山庄》吗
Anybody read "wuthering heights"?
电影版的呢 好样的巴尼
Anybody see the movie? Barney.
你去帮忙写篇观后感 甜点时间之前我需要你写五页纸出来
You got a book report due. I need five pages by dessert.
鲍伯·邓肯 算你走运 我多买了点豆子
Bob Duncan, you are so lucky I bought extra beans.
弗拉佛曼先生 我已准备好应对大量的特写镜头了
I'm ready for my close-up, Mr. Flufferman.
是吗 关于这个 我收到了你的邮件
Yeah, about that, I got your email,
看到了你在剧本上做的改动
Saw that you made some changes to the script.
-不用谢 -没想谢你
- You're welcome. - Yeah.
其实呢 我们也做了一些改动 人员上的变动
Actually we also made some changes... some casting changes.
-什么 -是吗
- What? - Oh.
不好意思 等我一下
Oh, give me a minute.
盖比 我的心肝儿 他们炒你鱿鱼了
Gabe, honey, they're replacing you.
噢 不是的 不是 不是
Oh, no. No no no no.
不是这样的 我门炒的是你 不是他
No, we're not replacing him. We're replacing you.
什么 是我
What? Me?
我吗
Me?
我可是这条广告的主角
I'm the star of the commercial.
呃 也许你是自己广告里的主角
Uh, you may be the star of your commercial.
他才是我们广告里的主角
He's the star of our commercial.
对她仁慈点儿 丹尼 她也是出于好意
Go easy on her, Danny. She means well.
不用了 祝你们能找到一个
Well, good luck finding someone.
能够与我相匹敌的人选
Who can replace this.
好吧 嘿 你会说英语吗
Um, hey, you speak English?
-会啊 -你可以回家了
- Yes. - You've been replaced.
哇 你比起她来更像我妈妈
Wow, you actually look more like my mom than she does.
好了
Okay.
进来吧
Come on in.
出什么问题了吗
Is something wrong?
为什么你认为出问题了
Why would you think something's wrong?
因为你打电话邀请我过来
'Cause you called and invited me over.
你以前可从未这样过
You've never done that before.
不如先坐下吧
Why don't you have a seat?
天啊 果真出问题了
Oh no, something is wrong.
好了 听着 事情是这样的
Okay. So, um, here's the thing.
我做了个梦
I had a dream.
还梦到了你
And you were in it.
你的眼镜起雾了
And your glasses are fogging up so...
简单地说 在梦里
Anyway, in... in the dream,
我们接吻了
We kissed.
而且感觉还不错
And it was a good kiss.
眼镜上又有雾了
There go your glasses again.
不管怎样 我认为
Anyway, I thought.
鉴于我们在表演中有吻戏
Since we have to kiss in the show,
也许我们先在这里亲一下比较好
Maybe it might be a good idea if we kiss here first.
你知道的 就像 就像彩排
You know, like a... like a rehearsal.
这样我们就可以了解到其中滋味
That way we can find out if it means anything.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
想赞同你的想法
Trying to say okay.
那好吧 就这么定了
All right, okay.
让我们携手度过这道难关
Well, let's get this over with then.
不敢相信这真的发生了
I can't believe this is really happening.
自从九岁起我就梦想着
I've been dreaming about this since I was nine years old.
看来我的梦想要成真了 这绝对会超完美的
I'm really gonna kiss Teddy Duncan. And it's gonna be perfect.
不管 豁出去了
Here goes nothing.
-等等 -干吗
- Wait. - What?
如果不会呢
What if it isn't?
-什么不会啊 -吻 如果不完美怎么办
- What if what isn't? - The kiss... what if it isn't perfect?
那更好 说明咱俩之间只是纯洁的友谊
Well, then we'll know that there's nothing between us.
-快把嘴撅起来 -算了 泰迪
- Now pucker up. - No, Teddy.
如果这个吻不是完美的 那我的梦想也破裂了
If the kiss isn't perfect, I lose my dream.
少废话 多亲亲
Less yakking, more smacking.
不要 放开我 我是不会亲你的
No no no! I'm not gonna kiss you.
你要亲我 我需要了解
Yes you are! I need to know.
我需要不了解
And I need to not know.
-亲我 -不 饶了我吧
- Kiss me! - No! Leave me alone!
那好吧 反正在表演上还是要亲的
Well, you're gonna have to kiss me at work.
-不会的 我辞职 -你狠
- No I won't. I quit. - Ah!
给我回来 快亲我 你个胆小鬼
Get back here and kiss me, you little wimp!
好啊 达布尼太太
Hi, Mrs. Dabney.
各就各位 冒险天地广告第一场
All right, super adventureland commercial take one.
开始
And action!
我爱死新版冒险天地了
I love the new super adventureland!
过山车更快了 而且排队时间更短了
The rides are faster and the lines are shorter.
新版冒险天地太棒了
The new super adventureland is awesome.
停
Cut!
呃
Uh...
你 你干什么呢
What... what are you doing?
遛弯儿
Walking.
好了 我们说是让你当龙套
Okay, we said that you could be an extra.
意思是让你走个过场 明白吗 不是让你抢镜头
And that means you walk, all right? And not in place.
好了 大家归位 准备好 重头再来
Okay, everybody back to one. Let's go. From the top.
预备
Here we go.
开始
And action.
我爱死新版冒险天地了
I love the new super adventureland!
过山车更快了 而且排队时间更短了
The rides are faster and the lines are shorter.
新版冒险天地太棒了
The new super adventureland is awesome.
而且更安全
And safer too.
停
Cut!
你 你又搞什么
What... what are you doing?
抱歉 呃 你说过不想让我说那句话吗
I'm sorry. Um, did you not want me to say that anymore?
没有 我没说
No, I didn't.
那好吧 关于这些 你应该说清楚点儿
Okay, well, you should be more clear about that.
再来一次
One more time.
请大家各就各位
Please, everybody, here we go.
听好了 别再出岔子了
Okay. Not rocket science.
开始
And action.
我爱死新版冒险天地了
I love the new super adventureland!
过山车更快了 而且排队时间更短了
The rides are faster and the lines are shorter.
新版冒险天地太棒了
The new super adventureland is awesome.
而且更安全
And safer too.
真的呦
And how!
停 保安
Cut. Security.
什么 哥们儿 放我下来
What? Guys, put me down.
谢天谢地把她弄走了
Ah, thank goodness that is over.
没有她捣乱 一切都会很顺利的
It's gonna be a lot easier without her.
而且更安全
And safer too.
特大新闻 我得了个不及格
Great news... I am getting an "F"
在“三好学”上
In "trigometry."
-不会吧 -语文课上同样悲剧
- What? - And I'm not doing so hot in English either.
请转告巴尼 在《呼啸山庄》中没人
Please tell Barney that no one in "wuthering heights"
手握激光剑
Carried a lightsaber.
-噢 PJ 别这样 -老爸 对不起了
- Oh, P.J., come on. - Dad, I'm sorry,
我不再给你做饭了
But I can't cook for you anymore.
我的成绩一落千丈 而且对于你的健康也不利
My grades are suffering and it's not healthy for you.
自从我下厨后 你长了多少肉
How much weight have you put on since I've been cooking?
-两磅 -说实话
- Two pounds. - Dad?
九磅
Nine pounds.
我们要回归正轨
We gotta get back to the way it was.
回归到你那苗条的身材 我那永恒的“及格”
When you were slim and I was getting solid "D"s.
看来你说得对
I guess you're right.
查莉 你能给爸爸做顿饭吗
Charlie, can you cook for daddy?
不 爸爸
No, daddy.
嗨 嗨 你肯定是新来的青蛙
Oh hi. Hi. You must be the new frog.
我是公主
I'm the princess.
我只想 和你打声招呼 因为我们以后要一起工作
I just... I wanted to say hello since we'll be working.
还要亲亲
And kissing together.
真庆幸他们召来了新人进来
I'm so glad they brought someone new in here.
我和以前那只青蛙有点儿纠结
Things got kind of complicated with the old frog.
所以你我搭配 干活绝对不累
So with you and me, it's gonna be nice and simple.
嘿 泰迪
Hey, Teddy.
斯宾塞
Spencer?
天啊 真会逗我玩
Aw, you gotta be kidding me.
听好了 查莉 这是怪异的一周
Well, Charlie, it's been a strange week.
呃 我梦到有只青蛙 同时也是我的王子
Um, I had a dream that my frog was a prince.
后来我的前男友穿着青蛙戏服出现了
And then my ex-prince showed up as a frog.
如今我要不停的吻他
And now I have to kiss him over and over.
请继续收看
Stay tuned.
嘿 老妈 你干啥呢
Hey, mom, what you doin'?
溜达
Just walking.
抢镜头吗
In place?
你不是也在抢我镜头吗
Don't you ever do that?
快闪人
Keep moving.
继续走
Go on.
看见了吧 这就是咱妈
Well, that's our mom.
她一看见镜头就两眼放光
She sees a camera and she can't help herself.
祝你好运喽 查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
没错呦
And how.
嘿 那是什么东西
Hey, what is that thing?
我在冒险天地礼品店买的
I bought it at the super adventureland gift shop.
-是台时光机 -饶了我吧 鲍伯
- It's a time machine. - Oh, for heaven's sakes, Bob.
你为什么总是把钱浪费在这种傻缺玩意上
Why would you waste your money on something as stupid as that?
店主说这东西能用 嘿 不如这样
The guy said it works. Hey, you know what?
我把时间设在几天前
I'm gonna set it back for a couple of days ago.
听好了 同志们 这是一份时刻表
All right, everyone, here's the schedule.
关于今天的冒险天地之旅
For today's trip to super adventureland.
我把每件事的进程都安排妥当了
I planned everything to the minute.
八点五十七启程
Depart promptly at 8:57 A.M.;
九点三十三到达冒天停车场
9:33 a.M.A.L. Parking lot,
我的七舅姥爷啊
Oh my gosh.
-有问题 -冒天代表“冒险天地”
- Question. - S.A.L. Stands for "super adventureland."
谢谢
Thank you.
真的显灵了
It really works.
你又在干什么
What're you doing?
调到这四个孩子出生之前
Setting this to before we had kids.